wpinsite.com 2012-05-11

# Privacy Policy - WPInsite

## WP Insite adheres to the following privacy policies:

Your privacy is important to us, and our policy is simple: we will collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Site unless you choose to provide that information . This Privacy Policy does not describe information collection practices on other sites, including those linked to or from the Site.

## Use of personal information & Site Usage:

You can visit many portions of the Site without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. We collect your personal information only with your informed consent. We use your information for personalisation, identification, and communication. We do not sell or redistribute your personal information outside of [WPInsite](http://www.wpinsite.com/ "WPInsite"). Information on your domain type, browser used and your IP address are collected and used for statistical purposes only, which will be used to improve the content of our web page.

## Failure to provide personal information:

If requested information is not provided, WPInsite may be unable to complete a transaction or it may impede our ability to provide a requested service.

## Spam Act 2003 Compliance

**New Email Broadcasting Laws**  
The Spam Act 2003 came into effect on the 10 th of April 2004 , throughout Australia . The Act refers to spam as “unsolicited commercial electronic messaging”.

The act requires that we get your explicit permission to send you our email specials and promotions. If you no longer wish to receive communication from us, please unsubscribe from our mailing list, [contact us](http://www.wpinsite.com/contact-us "contact us") by email, phone, fax or mail.

Important Note: The WPInsite email database is managed in accordance with Privacy Act 1988 (Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000 and it’s email marketing practices comply with the provisions of the Spam Act 2003.

Any request to be removed from the ANCOLD email database will be acted on within 24 hours of receipt of that advice, whether that advice be by email or phone.

## Links

This Site contains links to third-party Web sites that are not under the control of WPInsite. WPInsite makes no representations whatsoever about any other Web site to which you may have access through this Site. WPInsite provides these links merely as a convenience and the inclusion of such links does not imply that WPInsite endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content or uses of such Web sites.

## Product Support

If you require assistance or have any questions, please visit the “Contact Us” page.

## Copyright © / Trademarks (TM)

The images and materials found in the Web site are copyrighted or otherwise proprietary and may be not be downloaded and/or reprinted for any reason without prior consent. Permission to reprint or electronically reproduce any document, stills, audio, video footage or any other materials in whole or in part for any reason is expressly prohibited, unless prior written consent is obtained from the respective copyright holder(s).
